all rights reserved. copyright © 2018
Kinoshita Yuka
Physicalего
Bye bye!
Oh!
Thank you!
That's all!
We are the SONOSCO of the world!
Thank you for coming to see us!
Thank you!
Party!
Let's make this day a great one!
Next is the party!
Party!
Party people!
I want to eat sushi!
I want to go to the beach!
Yeah!
Don't forget
what we feel!
We are all party people!
But...
It's okay.
I'm not scared.
I'm here now.
VIVA!
I'm going to dance.
I'm here now.
It's okay.
I'm not scared.
I'm here now.
VIVA!
It's okay.
The wedding party is over.
I don't care about the mirror.
I'm scared.
I feel good.
Sushi for breakfast.
I'm going to dance.
It's okay.
I'm here now.
Let's go!
I want to eat!
But you know, before the live,
I'll make you a pimple!
No way!
Welcome!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Let's eat!
I wonder if the lighting is changed.
I'm ugly after the lesson.
It's so good.
It's really good.
There is a camera.
Really?
Good morning.
Your bangs are short.
Santa Claus is here.
You haveansen open the door fast.
A strange handling way.
Thank you.
I just realized.
You realized.
I realized.
Why, why?
Let's go, let's go.
The audience seats, the audience seats.
You're drunk.
Am I?
Who wants to go to the audience seats?
Let's go.
Wow.
Wow, Tsukiko.
Look, look.
My ID photo.
Isn't it cute?
That's it.
Isn't 15km crazy?
Isn't it amazing?
It's a luxury.
This is Wakarin's private property.
The view of the third floor.
Look! Who is it?
Wow!
What a view!
Galpi!
Wow!
It was closer than I thought.
Was it this close?
Right?
You can see it well.
I was so nervous that I couldn't see
anything.
The shape of the stage is different
from the last time.
I agree.
I was nervous because I had no makeup
on.
It was a tough stage.
I agree.
To be continued.
kungfu
I'm going to put the coffee in the cup.
Merry Christmas!
Please.
I put the coffee in the cup.
I can't see it.
I did it.
I didn't put the coffee in the cup yet,
so I put it in the cup.
I'm not good at it.
I'm going to check it.
I finished it.
I think it was a good year-end party.
Please look forward to the next video.
See you!
OK!